Their Backs
(サクラ)まだチャクラが足りない クッ。
Not yet... I don't have
enough chakra yet…
(チョウジ)ぬぉ～ ぎぃ～！
(いの)グッ… 起きろチョウジ！ チョウジ！
Wake up, Choji!
Choji!
(サヤ)あなた
何してくれちゃうのかしら。
What will you do next,
私のお人形さんは…。
my dear puppet?
お前の人形なんかじゃない！
He's not your puppet!
私の仲間だ！
He's my friend!
何するのよ！
What are you doing?
チョウジの中から出ていけ！
Get out of Choji!
出ていくのは
あなたのほうですわ！
You're the one who's getting out!
うっ… ま 負けない。
I-I won't lose!
山中一族が 心転身で
負けるわけにはいかないのよ！
There's no way the Yamanaka Clan's
Mind Transfer Jutsu will be defeated!
あぁ～！
ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
(チョウジ)グ グ グ… フンッ！
いの！
Ino?!
あっ…。
(サナ)お姉様！
Sister!
(マムシ)お嬢！
Lady Saya!
私の術が…。
My jutsu…
私の術が敗れ…。
My jutsu was undone! No!
敗れてない… 負けてない！
It wasn't undone...
I didn't lose!
負けてない！
負けてなんかいない！
I didn't…!
There's no way I'd lose!
(マムシ/サナ)あぁ～！
うっ…。
いの！ 勝ったのね！
Ino!
You did it!
ハァ ハァ ハァ。
うっ うぅ… えっ？
いの！ サクラ！
Ino! Sakura!
(サクラ)傀儡人形。
A puppet…?!
(いの)まさか…。
It can't be!
(マムシ)ここだ！ サナお嬢。
Over here! Lady Sana!
(サナ)マムシ 生きてる？
Mamushi, you're alive?
あったりめえだ。
お姉様は？
Damned right I am!
What about…Elder Sister?
お嬢！
お姉様 ご無事で？
Lady Saya!
Elder Sister, you're all right!
(サヤ)私はね。 でも➡
I'm okay…
But my doll is broken.
私の人形が壊されてしまった。
サヤお嬢の術が敗れるとは。
I can't believe your jutsu
was defeated…Lady Saya.
あ～？
ひいっ。
What?!
(サヤ)私は負けてない 負けてない。
負けてないんだ！
I did not lose! I didn't!
I did not lose!
I don't care about
the Chunin Exams anymore.
もう中忍試験なんて
どうだっていい。
Revenge! We're getting revenge!
復讐… 復讐するのよ。
Lady Saya…
サヤお嬢 でもどうやって？
But how…?
I'm going to turn them
into puppets
あいつらを傀儡にして10年間
便所掃除をさせてやる！
and make them clean toilets
for ten years…!
ひい～っ！
さすがですわ お姉様。
なんと えげつないことを。
As expected, Sister!
That's so depraved!
ウッフッフ… 木ノ葉の３人のうち➡
Those three from
the Hidden Leaf…
あの金髪は感知タイプ。
I'm going to get that
blonde Sensory-type!
そいつを逆に利用してやるわ。
サナ わかるわね？
You know what to do, right, Sana?
Of course, Sister.
ええ お姉様。
ハァ ハァ ハァ。
ハァ ハァ。
《チョウジも いのも➡
Choji and Ino have used up their chakra
due to all these battles.
連戦でチャクラを削ってる。
もう体力も気力も限界。
Their strength and willpower
are at their limits!
次に敵が襲ってきたら 私が…》
When the enemy attacks again,
it'll be up to me…!
《サクラ : あの頃の私は➡
Back then…
サスケ君やナルトに守られてばかりいた。
all I ever did was have
Sasuke and Naruto protect me.
今の私なら➡
Now, I should be able
to protect them.
２人を守れるはず。
あの時のサスケ君や➡
Like Sasuke…
and Naruto did back then!
ナルトみたいに！》
(自来也)さて 今日は➡
All right, today we're going to
step up our training much more.
今までの修業から
更にステップアップさせる。
(自来也)少し実験的な試みになる。
It will be like an experiment…
I don't even know
what might happen.
わしにも何が起こるか わからん。
覚悟はできておるな？
Are you prepared?
(ナルト)お おう！
Y-Yeah!
Let's just do it!
とにかく やってみるってばよ！
うむ 出て来い ゲロ寅！
Good.
Come on out, Gerotora!
I have a bad feeling about this…
(ゲロ寅)嫌な感じじゃのう。
Anytime you summon me,
it means you…
お前がわしを呼ぶってことは…。
That's right. I want you to loosen
the Nine-Tails' seal just a little.
さよう ほんの少しだけ➡
九尾の封印を開けるんだのう。
えっ？
(ゲロ寅)言っておくが
わしは反対じゃ。
Well, let me just start off
by saying, I'm opposed to this.
九尾は人間ごときに
どうこうできるものではない。
The Nine Tails cannot be
controlled by mere humans.
That's why I've taken
the time to make sure.
だからこそ時間をかけて
見極めてきた。
《自来也 : 今までの修業で
尾が２本になるまでなら➡
With all the training he's put in,
I know that Naruto can maintain
his own psyche up to
a two-tail transformation.
ナルトが自我を保てることは
わかっている。
それが どこまで可能か➡
We need to know
how much farther is possible.
知っておく必要があるんでのう》
大丈夫なのか？ 小僧。
Can you handle it, kid?
封印を開けるということは➡
Opening the seal means that
九尾の影響を
もろに受けるということだ。
the Nine Tails influence
will grow stronger.
Can you say for sure that
のみ込まれて暴走しないと➡
he won't take you over
and run amok?
本当に言い切れるのか？
それは…。
Well, I…
(自来也)クハッハッハッ…。
Well, if worse comes to worst,
なあに いざというときは➡
I, Jiraiya, one of the Legendary Sannin,
will stop him even if it kills me.
この伝説の三忍 自来也様が➡
体を張って 止めるだけよ！
エロ仙人…。
Pervy Sage…
それに わしはナルトがこの術を➡
Besides, I have faith that
Naruto will master this jutsu.
会得すると信じておる。
九尾をナルトの中に封印した➡
As did the Fourth Hokage
who sealed the Nine Tails in Naruto.
四代目 火影と同じようにな。
おう！
Yeah!
じゃあ いくぞ。
ああ。
All right then, let's begin.
Right!
そりゃあ！
Here we go!
うっ。
(ゲロ寅)あっという間に２本。
Two tails in an instant…
Hey, there's the third tail!
おいっ！ ３本目が出たぞ！
そこだ ナルト！
Now, Naruto!
そこでチャクラを抑えろ。
Suppress your chakra now!
くっ… うぅ！
くっ…。
Suppress yourself!
己を抑えるんじゃ！
I got that!
わかってるってばよ！ くっ。
《でも なんだ？
What is this irritating feeling?
このイライラする感じ…。
憎くて 憎くて➡
It's bitter and hateful…
腹ん中が真っ黒に
なっていくみてえだ！》
It feels like my insides
are turning black!
(九喇嘛)お前に協力してやろう。
I'll cooperate with you.
ん？
Y-You are…?
お お前は…。
(九喇嘛)遠慮することはない。
Don't hold back.
力が欲しいんだろう？
You want power, don't you?
Cut it out!
やめろ！ うわっ。
しかし 哀れを通り越して
滑稽だな。
You know it's pretty pathetic…
The guy you're trying
to bring back left the village...
お前が必死に
取り戻そうとしている男は➡
自ら里を捨てた。
とっくに お前のことなど忘れて
マシな相手と組んでるだろうに。
He forgot
about you long ago…
and he's teamed up with
a better partner.
うるせえ！ 引っ込んでろ！
Shut up and go back!
ゴホッ…。
(九喇嘛)バカが！
Idiot… If anyone goes back…
it's you!
引っ込むのは お前のほうだ。
やはり 無謀だったんじゃ！
It was a reckless idea, after all.
しかたないのう。
Such a pity.
Gerotora, stay back!
ゲロ寅 お前は下がっとれ！
I'll stop Naruto.
ナルトは わしが止める！
おお～っ!!
ここは？
Where am I?
(自来也)起きたか？
You're awake...
エロ仙人？
Pervy Sage!
うっ… く… これって。
What happened?!
決まっておろう。
暴走したお前を抑えてこのザマよ。
Isn't it obvious?
You went on a rampage,
so I held you down and
this is the result.
肋やら何やら
やっちまったらしい。
It's just some broken ribs
and what not…
うっ…。
俺のせいで。
I did that…?
お前のせいではない。
今回は わしの判断ミスだ。
It's not your fault.
I made the wrong call.
I underestimated some things.
少し甘く見すぎていたのう。
エロ仙人 俺…。
Pervy Sage… I…
詫びることはない。
修業に失敗は つきものじゃ。
Don't apologize.
Sometimes, training goes wrong.
It's normal.
But…!
でも！
俺 あいつの挑発に乗っちまって。
He provoked me and I gave in!
それで？ ゲロ寅の言うとおり➡
So?
Was Gerotora right?
やはり 無理だと諦めるか？
Will you give up because
it's impossible?
３本目までは なんとか
自分の意識を保てたんだ。
I held onto my consciousness
up to three tails.
But I felt this immense power…
すげえ力が湧いてきて…。
And I realized that this jutsu
is absolutely necessary.
この術が必要だって
はっきりわかった。
今は無理でも 絶対に諦めねえ。
Even if it's impossible for me now,
I'll never give up!
俺を信じてくれた エロ仙人と
四代目の気持は裏切れねえ！
I won't betray the faith
you and the Fourth Hokage
put into me, Pervy Sage!
フン…。
I always knew it couldn't be
dealt with in a straightforward manner...
もともと 一筋縄でいかんことは
わかっておった。
もう一度 方法を考える➡
We just have to
figure out some other way.
必要があるのう。 うっ…。
《ナルトは 必ずどこかで
頑張って修業をしてる。
I know that Naruto is somewhere
training hard right now…!
私も➡
And I…can't waste my time
feeling sorry for myself!
こんなところで
弱音を吐くわけにはいかない！》
砂嵐の術！
Sand Storm Jutsu!
Well, Elder Sister…
I leave the rest up to you.
じゃあ お姉様
あとは よろしく。
頼むぜ サヤお嬢。
We're counting on you, Lady Saya.
呪いの砂人形の術！
Cursed Sand Puppet Jutsu!
なんだって いきなり
僕たちの周りだけ砂嵐が？
Why did a sand storm
suddenly start up only around us?
不自然よ！ 攻撃を受けてると
とらえるべきじゃない？
This is unnatural!
We have to consider this
some kind of attack!
あいつらね？
まだ懲りてないなんて！
It's them…
Haven't they learned
their lesson?
視界を塞いで
襲ってくるつもりよ。
They plan to limit our vision,
then attack!
(チョウジ)やつらのほうが
地の利があるからね。
They do have
the ground advantage.
大丈夫！ ２人にも➡
Don't worry!
I'll send you whatever
images I can grab.
私のとらえたイメージを送るから！
うっ…。
いの！
Ino!
大丈夫？ さっきから ずっと
感知能力 全開じゃない！
Are you okay?
You've been in full Sensory Perception
mode for an awfully long while.
このくらい まだ平気よ！
I can still handle this…
呪いの砂人形の術
まだまだ増えるわよ。
My Cursed Sand Puppet Jutsu…
will bring forth many, many more.
あの感知タイプの金髪女
私の操りの術を抑え込むのに➡
That blonde Sensory-type
is near exhaustion
相当のチャクラを使って
疲れ切っている。
from using so much chakra
to ward off my jutsu…
そのうえでの呪い人形…。
And now, all these Cursed Puppets…
(サヤ)この数を感知するのは
相当な負担のはず。
Using Sensory Perception on this
many has to be quite a burden.
ハァ ハァ ハァ…。
うぅっ！
(サヤ)クックック… マムシ。
Mamushi…
てや～っ！
サナ お願いね。
Roger!
Take over, Sana.
はい お姉様。
Yes, Elder Sister.
砂衣の術！
Sand Cloak Jutsu!
くっ…。
いの！ これ以上無理しないで！
Ino!
Don't push yourself
so hard anymore!
でも…。
３人で それぞれの方向を➡
But…
If each of us can guard
our own line of sight,
警戒すれば 何とかなるよ。
わかったわ。
we'll manage somehow!
All right.
心伝身で３人の視界を
ひとつにつなぐ。
I'll use Mind Transmission Jutsu
to connect what we each see.
それなら 負担も軽くなるから。
That'll take some of
the burden off of me.
うっ！ ん？
いける！ いの こいつら
結構もろいよ！
It's working!
Ino! These guys are pretty weak.
Yes… This'll work!
そうね これなら！
だぁ～！
いくらでも来い！
全部 蹴散らしてやる！
Keep on coming at me!
I'll kick your butts!
えっ!?
うっ うわぁ～！
チョウジ！
Choji!
(いの)サクラ！ うぅっ！
Sakura!
いの！ うぉ～！
Ino!
(マムシ)まあいい
すぐに毒がまわる。
It's fine. The poison will start
spreading soon…
お前たちは すぐに動けなくなる
ハッハッハ…。
And you won't be able to move!
チョウジ！ いの！
Choji! Ino!
このくらい 何てことはないわ。
This…is nothing.
うん 毒が全身にまわる前に
あいつら全部 叩き潰す！
Yeah! I'll pulverize them all
before the poison starts spreading
throughout my body!
《サクラ : また私は守られてる…》
I'm still the one being protected…
《これじゃいけない。
I can't let this happen…
私は変わったんだから！》
After all, I changed!
《早くチャクラを…
あのときのように！》
I must hurry with my chakra…
Like that time…
((早く治療しなければ
この人は死んでしまいます！
We have to treat him quickly
or he'll die!
(サクラ)急いで綱手様を
呼びに行かなくては。
We must hurry and get Lady Tsunade…
うぅ～！
とにかく 集中治療室へ。
はい。
Take him to the ICU immediately!
Right!
あ…。
(綱手)手術も 前に出て戦うことも
許可することはできんぞ！
I can't allow you to
do any surgery
or go out into the battlefront!
でも 綱手様を待っていたら
患者が死ぬ。
But… If we wait for Lady Tsunade,
the patient will die…
(私がやるしかない))
SURGERY IN PROGRESS
I just have to do it!
これは…。
This is…?!
Sakura's feelings are
flooding into me
心伝身の術で
サクラの心が入ってきている!?
through the Mind Transmission Jutsu…?!
((うぅ～！
《私しかいないんだ… 私が！
There's only me. Just me…
今こそ チャクラのコントロールを。
This is the time for chakra control…
ダメだ！ チャクラが足りない！
It's no good.
I don't have enough chakra…
サスケ君… ナルト！
Sasuke… Naruto…
私 こんなときまで
２人に頼って…》
I…
I'm still depending on those two…
even at a time like this.
うわぁ～！ うぅ…。
《できないなんて言えない。
No more saying, "I can't."
私ができなければ この人が死ぬ！
Unless I do it, this man will die.
もっとチャクラを！
I need more chakra…
もっと！
More…
私が… 私の力で 私の意志で…》
I must do it…
With my own strength…
With my own willpower!
《少しだけど チャクラが回復した。
It's slight, but I feel
my chakra replenishing…
やれる！ 必ずこの人を助ける！》
I can do it!
I will save this man!
(綱手)中忍試験に出るだと？
You're going to take
the Chunin Exams?
本気か？
お願いします。
Are you serious?
Please…
許可はできんと言ったはずだ。
I already told you I can't authorize it.
百豪のチャクラを溜めるダムと
日常に使うチャクラを溜めるダム…。
The dam to reserve chakra
from the 100 Healings Jutsu…
and the dam to store chakra
I normally use…
２つのチャクラをコントロールすることで
手術にも成功しました。
I was able to control
both of these dams
and successfully performed surgery.
どこまで できるか
試験に参加することで➡
I want to see how far I can go.
I want to push myself as far as I can
by participating in the Exams.
自分を追い込んでみたいんです。
私は まだまだ未熟です。
でも こんな私を➡
I'm still a novice…
yet Choji and Ino asked me
to join them.
いのとチョウジが誘ってくれました。
They asked me to take
the Chunin Exams with them.
一緒に中忍試験に出ようって。
私を信頼してくれた２人にも
応えたいんです！
I want to honor their trust in me!
お願いします！
Please!
AUTHORIZED
(綱手)持っていけ。
Take this with you.
ありがとうございます！
ただし➡
Thank you very much!
However…
中忍試験で起こることは
すべて 自己責任だ。
Whatever happens at the Chunin Exams
will be your sole responsibility.
(綱手)いいな？
はい！))
Understood?
Yes!
I see…
そうか…。
サクラは そんな事情をおして
僕たちのために…。
You were under that
kind of pressure,
yet you came just for us…
知らなかった…。
We didn't know…
and we made you come…
私が無理に誘ったばっかりに…。
違うの！
これは誰のためでもない！
You're wrong!
I didn't do this for you!
I did it for me… Me alone.
私自身！ 私のためなの…。
I've always just looked at
《いつもナルトやサスケ君の背中ばかり
追ってきた➡
Naruto and Sasuke's backs
from behind.
私自身に対する挑戦！
I'm challenging myself this time.
いの… チョウジ…。
Ino… Choji…
私を信じてくれて ありがとう。
Thank you for believing in me.
私を誘ってくれて
本当に… 本当に…。
Thank you for asking me to join you…
ありがとう》
Thank you so much.
デブと金髪は
もう動けませんわ お姉様。
Elder Sister, the fatso and
the blonde can't move anymore.
おでこもすぐに…。
Big forehead will soon…
おでこのチャクラが
急激に上がってますわ！
Big forehead's chakra
has suddenly spiked!
《チャクラが溜まった!!
チョウジといのは 私が絶対に守る！
一気に…》
終わらせる！
しゃ～んなろ～!!
(３人)うわ～!!
私は負けてない！ 負けてない！
負けてないんだ～！
(サナ)お姉様!!
負けてる！
これ絶対負けてるって！
(サヤ)マムシ！ お前100年 便所掃除!!
い～や～!!
ん…。
大丈夫？ 毒は抜いたから➡
じき痺れもとれるわ。
あ… ありがとう。
ううん。 私 ２人に謝らないと。
え？
心伝身で見たでしょ？
２人を私の挑戦に
つきあわせてしまった…。
まったくよね！
な～んてね。
やっぱりあんたを
誘ってよかったわ。
いの…。
うん！ 誘ってよかったよ。
この３人なら
どんなやつらにだって➡
勝てる気がするよ。
２人とも…。
あ… えっと…。
プッハハハハ！
アハハハハ！
(サクラ)もう 何よぉ ２人とも！
さあ 中央塔へ向かうよ！
二次試験 突破まで あと少し!!
チョウジ… いの…
ほんとにありがとう。
オープニングは美空ひばりさんの
名曲からスタートしましょう。
皆さんも
ご一緒に歌ってください。